# **Cody Murray**

Ambitious full-stack developer with strong foundational knowledge of web development languages and frameworks. Eager to combine past experience working in team environments with new skills to make a meaningful contribution to an organization and future projects.

505 Howard Road
Spencer, TN 38585
(765) 318-0122
codakmurraki@gmail.com
github.com/CodyMurr
linkedin.com/in/cody-w-murray/

#### **PROJECTS**

### Simon — HTML/CSS/JS

A client-side browser game emulating the classic HASBRO memory game. Built using HTML, CSS, and vanilla Javascript and deployed to Github Pages - <a href="mailto:codymurr.github.io/Simon/">codymurr.github.io/Simon/</a>

github.com/CodyMurr/Simon

Cors — Python3/Django/PostgreSQL

A full-stack, ecommerce web application built in collaboration with three fellow SEI students while attending General Assembly. Minimalistic and elegant, the app's intent is to provide a simplified online shopping experience for consumers of high-end skin care products. Technologies used are the Django framework, Python3, and PostgreSQL. Deployed via Heroku - <a href="mailto:cors-sei.herokuapp.com/">cors-sei.herokuapp.com/</a>

github.com/CodyMurr/cors-project

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Rock Solid Concrete Inc**, Cookeville, TN — *Concrete Finisher*

July 2021 - January 2022

Aided in excavation, preparation and completion of a multitude of commercial and residential concrete projects. Demonstrated ability to adapt to changing work environments and collaborate with crew members to see projects to completion with minimal discrepancies.

# **Smith Construction Group**, Dayton, OH — Concrete Foreman

November 2014 - February 2021

Oversaw the layout, excavation, and placement of 20+ commercial fueling station foundations while maintaining a clear line of communication with project managers, superintendents, and sub-contractors.

# **U.S. Navy**, FPO/AP — Aviation Ordnanceman

September 2011 - 2014

Performed maintenance on ship's manned weapon systems and ammo magazines and logged all

#### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS Markdown

Javascript

**JQuery** 

Mongoose/MongoDB

Node

**Express** 

React

Handlebars

Python3

Django

PostgreSQL

Heroku

Git/Github

VS Code

Command Line/Shell

equipment/weapons signed out by qualified personnel. Worked in diverse team environments to execute complex tasks and demonstrate a competent level of judgment.

#### **EDUCATION**

# White County High School, Sparta, TN — Diploma

August 2007 - May 2011

**General Assembly,** Remote — *Certificate* Software Engineering Immersive Dec 2021 - March 2022